You'll live the adventure... You'll love its heroes.
The Ewok Adventure is a adventure, family, fantasy film directed by John Korty.
Wicket the Ewok and his friends agree to help two shipwrecked human
children, Mace and Cindel, on a quest to find their parents.
Mace Towani, played by Eric Walker.
Wicket W. Warrick, played by Warwick Davis.
Catarine Towani, played by Fionnula Flanagan.
Jeremitt Towani, played by Guy Boyd.
Cindel Towani, played by Aubree Miller.
Deej Warrick, played by Daniel Frishman.
The Ewok Adventure is a 1984 American television
film based in the Star Wars universe.
It takes place on the moon of Endor, and features the Ewoks, who help two
young human siblings as they try to locate their parents.
The film premiered on November 25, 1984 on ABC.
The film was given a limited international theatrical run, for which
it was retitled Caravan of Courage: An Ewok Adventure.
It was followed by a sequel, Ewoks: The Battle for Endor, in 1985.
The film explores themes of rescue, space marine,
monster, parent child relationship, magic.
The tone is thought_provoking.